{
    "subject": "resource/As_Long_as_It_Takes",
    "predicate": "ontology/previousWork",
    "object": "resource/The_Invitation_(Meredith_Andrews_album)",
    "human_readable": "The previous work of As Long as It Takes is The Invitation (Meredith Andrews album).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.925365149974823,
            "question": "Name the album that precedes 'As Long as It Takes' by Meredith Andrews."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8953417539596558,
            "question": "What was the previous musical release from Meredith Andrews before 'As Long as It Takes'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8825414776802063,
            "question": "What is the title of Meredith Andrews' album that came before 'As Long as It Takes'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8100401163101196,
            "question": "Before listening to 'As Long as It Takes', what album should you check out by Meredith Andrews?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7635557055473328,
            "question": "If you enjoyed 'As Long as It Takes', what album by Meredith Andrews should you listen to next?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6501471400260925,
            "question": "What album title follows 'The Invitation' in Meredith Andrews' discography?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6344470381736755,
            "question": "What is the album that came before 'As Long as It Takes'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6278848648071289,
            "question": "Which album is considered a predecessor to 'As Long as It Takes'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.580856442451477,
            "question": "What is the name of the album that preceded 'As Long as It Takes'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36097219586372375,
            "question": "Who is the artist behind the album 'The Invitation'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The previous work of As Long as It Takes is The Invitation (Meredith Andrews album).",
            "html": "dbpedia_959_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the album that preceded 'As Long as It Takes'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_959_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which album is considered a predecessor to 'As Long as It Takes'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_959_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the album that came before 'As Long as It Takes'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_959_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_959_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_959_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_959_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_959_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_959_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_959_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_959_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_959_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_959_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_959_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to evaluate more triples!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response to your query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents contain information about Meredith Andrews' music career, and specifically mention her debut project \"The Invitation\" and her second project \"As Long as It Takes\". This suggests that \"The Invitation\" is indeed the previous work of \"As Long as It Take\", which is an album by Meredith Andrews."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Meredith Andrews' albums, specifically mentioning that her third studio album is titled \"Worth It All\" and follows the release of \"The Invitation\" and \"As Long As It Takes.\" This supports the statement that \"The previous work of As Long as It Takes is The Invitation (Meredith Andrews album).\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}